Guide to the Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Printed Ephemera Collection on Organizations PE.036
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- S, 302344
  - School of Organic Education (Fairhope, AL), undated; 302463 (Box 88)
  - School of the Americas Watch (SOA Watch), 1996-; 302498 (Box 88)
  - School Stoppers Textbook, 1973; 325215 (Box 88)
  - Science Action Coordinating Committee (Massachusetts Institute of Technology), 1970, undated; 302465 (Box 88)
  - Science for the People, 1975-1984; 302466 (Box 88)
  - Science Holiday (Huntington Beach, CA), undated; 302467 (Box 88)
  - Scientists and Engineers for Social and Political Action, 1970-1972; 302468 (Box 88)
  - Scientists on Survival, Inc., 1964; 302469 (Box 88)
  - Scottsboro Defense Committee, 1933-1938; 302470 (Box 88)
  - Scottish Co-operative Convalescent Seaside Homes Association, 1904, undated; 302471 (Box 88)
  - Scottish League for the Taxation of Land Values, undated; 302472 (Box 88)
  - Scottish Socialist Sunday Schools, 1908; 302473 (Box 88)
  - Scratch Press (Minneapolis, MN), 1972; 302474 (Box 88)
  - Screen Players: Telephone Directory, 1920; 325216 (Box 88)
  - Sea Shepherd Conservation Society, 2010-; 325217 (Box 88)
  - Seattle Committee to End the War in Vietnam, undated; 373801 (Box 88)
  - Seattle Labor School, 1946; 302475 (Box 88)
  - Seattle Liberation Front, undated; 302476 (Box 88)
  - Seattle Women's Action Network for Peace and Justice (SWAN), undated; 302477 (Box 88)
  - Second World Defense (London), 1976; 302478 (Box 88)
  - Seize the Time, 1974; 302479 (Box 88)
  - Self Defense Committee of the 17 Victims of the Smith Act (New York, NY), 1951-1953; 302480 (Box 88)
  - Self Education Foundation, 2000; 373075 (Box 88)
  - Selma Project (Tuscaloosa, AL), 1973; 302481 (Box 88)
  - Selskabet Til Forskning I Arbejderbevgelsens Historie (Society for Research into Labour History) (Denmark), undated; 302482 (Box 88)
  - Sennacieca Asocio Tutmonda en Britio (Manifesto of Non-Nationalists) (Manchester), 1937; 302486 (Box 88)
  - Sentinel Printing Co. (Reading, PA), undated; 302487 (Box 88)
  - September 11 Families for Peaceful Tomorrows, 2002; 302488 (Box 88)
  - September Action Collective, undated; 373076 (Box 88)
  - Serviceman's Link to Peace, 1969-1970; 302489 (Box 88)
  - Sex Workers Action New York (SWANK), 2009-; 325218 (Box 88)
  - Sex Workers and Advocates for Rights and Decriminalization, 2001; 304348 (Box 88)
  - Sex Workers Outreach (Project SWOP), undated; 452608 (Box 88)
  - SF Newsreel ("Which Side Are You on" script), 325219 (Box 88)
  - Shac7 Support Fund, 2000-; 351039 (Box 88)
  - Sherman Institute (New York, NY), 1843; 302490 (Box 88)
  - Sherman Service, Inc., 1919-1925; 302491 (Box 88)
  - Shoshana (Pat Swinton) Defense Committee, undated; 372204 (Box 88)
  - Simian (London), 1971-1974; 302492 (Box 89)
  - Singlejack Books (San Pedro, CA), 1978-1984; 302493 (Box 89)
  - Sit-In For Survival, undated; 325230 (Box 89)
  - Situationist International I, 1967-1968, undated; 302494 (Box 89)
  - Situationist International II, 1967-1968, undated; 302495 (Box 89)
  - Sleepy Lagoon Defense Committee (Los Angeles, CA), 1944, undated; 302496 (Box 89)
  - Slingshot Collective (calendar), 2003-; 325231 (Box 89)
  - Slovenian American National Council (Chicago, IL), 1944; 302497 (Box 89)
  - SNAFU, 2004, undated; 373077 (Box 89)
  - S.O.C. (Save Our Community) (New York, NY), 1981; 302499 (Box 89)
  - Sociaal-Demokratische Partij In Nederland, 1909; 302500 (Box 89)
  - Social Anarchism (Baltimore, MD), 1997; 302501 (Box 89)
  - Social Democracy of Lettland, undated; 302502 (Box 89)
  - Social Democratic Federation (London), 1907; 302503 (Box 89)
  - Social Democratic Federation of America I, 1937; 302504 (Box 89)
  - Social Democratic Federation of America II, 1937; 302505 (Box 89)
  - Social Democratic Federation of America, 1938; 302506 (Box 89)
  - Social Democratic Federation of America, 1939; 302507 (Box 89)
  - Social Democratic Federation of America, undated; 302511 (Box 89)
  - Social Democratic Federation of America: German Speaking Branch, 1943; 302512 (Box 89)
  - Social Democratic Federation of America: New Jersey, 1936; 302513 (Box 89)
  - Social Democratic Federation of America (New York, NY), 1937; 302519 (Box 89)
  - Social Democratic Federation of America (New York, NY) I, 1938; 302520 (Box 89)
  - Social Democratic Federation of America (New York, NY) II, 1938; 302524 (Box 89)
  - Social Democratic Federation of America (New York, NY), 1939; 302525 (Box 89)
  - Social Democratic Federation of America (New York, NY), 1940; 302526 (Box 89)
  - Social Democratic Federation of America (New York, NY), 1941; 302527 (Box 89)
  - Social Democratic Federation of America (New York, NY), 1942; 302528 (Box 89)
  - Social Democratic Federation of America (New York, NY), 1943; 302529 (Box 89)
  - Social Democratic Federation of America (New York, NY), 1944; 302530 (Box 89)
  - Social Democratic Federation of America (New York, NY), 1945; 302532 (Box 89)
  - Social Democratic Federation of America (New York, NY), 1946; 302533 (Box 89)
  - Social Democratic Federation of America (New York, NY), 1947; 302534 (Box 89)
  - Social Democratic Federation of America (New York, NY), 1948; 302535 (Box 89)
  - Social Democratic Federation of America (New York, NY), 1949; 302536 (Box 89)
  - Social Democratic Federation of America (New York, NY), 1950; 302537 (Box 89)
  - Social Democratic Federation of America (New York, NY), 1951; 302538 (Box 89)
  - Social Democratic Federation of America (New York, NY), 1952; 302539 (Box 90)
  - Social Democratic Federation of America (New York, NY), 1953; 302540 (Box 90)
  - Social Democratic Federation of America (New York, NY), 1954; 302541 (Box 90)
  - Social Democratic Federation of America (New York, NY), 1956; 302542 (Box 90)
  - Social Democratic Federation of America (New York, NY), 1957; 302543 (Box 90)
  - Social Democratic Federation of America (New York, NY), 1958; 302544 (Box 90)
  - Social Democratic Federation of America (New York, NY), undated; 302545 (Box 90)
  - Social Democratic Federation of America (New York, NY): Youth Committee, 1941; 302546 (Box 90)
  - Social Democratic Federation of America (New York State), 1936, 1939; 302547 (Box 90)
  - Social Democratic League of America, 1916-1917; 302548 (Box 90)
  - Social Democratic Party (Great Britain), 1910; 302549 (Box 90)
  - Social Democratic Party of America, 1898, 1900; 302550 (Box 90)
  - Social Democratic Party of America, 1901-1904; 302551 (Box 90)
  - Social Democratic Party of America, undated; 302552 (Box 90)
  - Social Democratic Party of America: County Campaign Committee (Milwaukee County, WI) (election campaign handbook) I, 1912; 377467 (Box 90)
  - Social Democratic Party of America: County Campaign Committee (Milwaukee County, WI) (election campaign handbook) II, 1912; 377469 (Box 90)
  - Social Democratic Party of America (Massachusetts), 1912; 302553 (Box 90)
  - Social Democratic Party of America: National Campaign Committee, 1900; 377468 (Box 90)
  - Social Democratic Party of America (New York, NY), 1903; 302554 (Box 90)
  - Social Democratic Party of America (New York, NY), 1905; 302555 (Box 90)
  - Social Democratic Party of America (New York State), 1901-1908; 302556 (Box 90)
  - Social Democratic Party of Canada, undated; 302557 (Box 90)
  - Social Democratic Party of Denmark, 1990, undated; 302558 (Box 90)
  - Social Democratic Women's Society of America, undated; 302559 (Box 90)
  - Social Democrats U.S.A., 1973-1975; 302560 (Box 90)
  - Social Democrats U.S.A., 1976-; 302561 (Box 90)
  - Social Democrats U.S.A., undated; 302562 (Box 90)
  - Social Economic Foundation (New York, NY), 1936; 335504 (Box 90)
  - Social Economic Laboratory (New York, NY), 1936; 302563 (Box 90)
  - Social Graphics Company, 1983; 302564 (Box 90)
  - Social Insecurity, 1984-; 302565 (Box 90)
  - Social Movements Collection, 2012; 452634 (Box 90)
  - Social Revolution (London), 1976; 302566 (Box 90)
  - Social Revolutionary Anarchist Federation I, 1970s; 302567 (Box 90)
  - Social Revolutionary Anarchist Federation II, 1970s; 302568 (Box 90)
  - Social Science Club (Philadelphia, PA), undated; 302569 (Box 90)
  - Social Science Institute (Harborside, ME), undated; 302570 (Box 90)
  - Social Science Workshop (Washington, DC), undated; 302571 (Box 90)
  - Social Security Board, 1936; 325264 (Box 90)
  - Social Services Employees Union Local 371, undated; 547123 (Box 90)
  - Social Service Volunteers for Peace, undated; 373078 (Box 90)
  - Social Work Action for Welfare Rights (New York, NY), undated; 302572 (Box 90)
  - Socialism Conference, 2011; 422946 (Box 90)
  - Socialist Action, 1987-, undated; 328207 (Box 90)
  - Socialist Alliance (Australia), 2002; 302573 (Box 90)
  - Socialist Alternative, 2001-2004, undated; 373079 (Box 90)
  - Socialist Appeak Institute (Chicago, IL), 1937; 325267 (Box 90)
  - Socialist Call (New York, NY), 1936-1959; 302574 (Box 90)
  - Socialist Center for Education and Culture, undated; 302575 (Box 90)
  - Socialist Club (New York, NY), 1912; 302576 (Box 90)
  - Socialist Committee of Correspondence, 1970, undated; 302577 (Box 90)
  - Socialist Committee of Correspondence (Philadelphia, PA), undated; 302578 (Box 90)
  - Socialist Educational International, 1931; 302579 (Box 90)
  - Socialist Equality Party, 1996-2006; 302580 (Box 90)
  - Socialist-Feminist Conference (Yellow Springs, OH), 1975; 302581 (Box 90)
  - Socialist Forum (New York, NY), 1971-1976; 302582 (Box 90)
  - Socialist Labor Committee, 1960s; 302588 (Box 90)
  - Socialist Labor League (Great Britain) I, 1960-1970, undated; 325281 (Box 90)
  - Socialist Labor League (Great Britain) II, 1960-1970, undated; 302590 (Box 91)
  - Socialist Labor League (Great Britain) III, 1960-1970, undated; 302591 (Box 91)
  - Socialist Lawyers' Association, undated; 302592 (Box 91)
  - Socialist League, 1885-1892, 1934, undated; 302593 (Box 91)
  - Socialist League (Newark, NJ), undated; 325282 (Box 91)
  - Socialist Literary Society of Philadelphia, 1912; 325283 (Box 91)
  - Socialist Literature Company, undated; 302594 (Box 91)
  - Socialist Medical Association (Great Britain), 1975-1976, undated; 302595 (Box 91)
  - Socialist Organiser (London), 1985-1990; 302596 (Box 91)
  - Socialist Organizer, undated; 373082 (Box 91)
  - Socialist Organizing Committee (Chicago, IL), 1973; 302597 (Box 91)
  - Socialist Party (India), 1949-1956; 302606 (Box 91)
  - Socialist Party of Australia (pamphlet), undated; 302598 (Box 91)
  - Socialist Party of Azania, 2004; 412386 (Box 91)
  - Socialist Party of Canada, 1948, undated; 302599 (Box 91)
  - Socialist Party of Great Britain, 1914-; 302600 (Box 91)
  - Socialist Party of Great Britain, 1967-1974; 302601 (Box 91)
  - Socialist Party of Great Britain: Pamphlets I, 302602 (Box 91)
  - Socialist Party of Great Britain: Pamphlets II, 302603 (Box 91)
  - Socialist Party of Great Britain: Pamphlets III, 302604 (Box 91)
  - Socialist Party of Great Britain: Pamphlets IV, 302605 (Box 91)
  - Socialist Party of Ireland, 1955-; 325284 (Box 91)
  - Socialist Party of Uruguay (Partido Socialista del Uruguay), 1978; 305832 (Box 91)
  - Socialist Propaganda League of America, 1915-1916; 302607 (Box 91)
  - Socialist Publication Society (New York, NY), 1918; 302608 (Box 91)
  - Socialist Reconstruction, 1970-1971; 302609 (Box 92)
  - Socialist Scholars Conference, 1965-1970; 302610 (Box 92)
  - Socialist Scholars Conference, 1971-; 302611 (Box 92)
  - Socialist Society of the United States of America (includes Articles of Incorporation), 1955, undated; 302612 (Box 92)
  - Socialist Sociologists, 1974; 380150 (Box 92)
  - Socialist Sunday School Union, undated; 302613 (Box 92)
  - Socialist Tenants Union, undated; 302614 (Box 92)
  - Socialist Trade and Labor Alliance, 1899; 302615 (Box 92)
  - Socialist Union of Central and Eastern Europe, 1958-1961, undated; 302616 (Box 92)
  - Socialist Union Party (U.S.), undated; 302617 (Box 92)
  - Socialist Unity Party of Germany, 1967; 373083 (Box 92)
  - Socialist War Committee for a Righteous Peace, undated; 302618 (Box 92)
  - SocialistWorker.org, 2011; 412396 (Box 92)
  - Socialist Workers Party (Great Britain), 1977-1990, undated; 302619 (Box 92)
  - Socialist Workers Party (Great Britain): Pamphlets I, 1970-; 302620 (Box 92)
  - Socialist Workers Party (Great Britain): Pamphlets II, 1970-; 302621 (Box 92)
  - Socialist Workers Party (Great Britain): Pamphlets III, 1970-; 302622 (Box 92)
  - Socialist Workers Party (Great Britain): Pamphlets IV, 1970-; 302623 (Box 92)
  - Socialist Youth International, 1933; 302624 (Box 92)
  - Socialist Youth International: Press Service, 1925-1930; 302625 (Box 92)
  - Socialist Youth League (U.S.), 1945-; 302626 (Box 92)
  - Socialist Youth League (U.S.), undated; 302627 (Box 92)
  - Socialist Zionist Youth Movement (U.S.), undated; 302628 (Box 92)
  - Socialistic Co-operative Publishing Association, 1869-1911; 302629 (Box 92)
  - Sociendades Hispanas de los Estados Unidos de Norte America, 1964-1965; 302630 (Box 92)
  - Society for Cultural Relations with Foreign Countries, 1958-1960; 380151 (Box 92)
  - Society for Cultural Relations with the U.S.S.R. (Great Britain), 1952-19954; 302631 (Box 92)
  - Society for Friendship with Bulgaria (Great Britain), 1955-; 302632 (Box 92)
  - Society for Social Responsibility in Science, 1964; 302633 (Box 92)
  - Society for Socialist Inquiry and Propaganda: Study Guides, undated; 302634 (Box 92)
  - Society for the Prevention of World War III (New York, NY), 1944; 302635 (Box 92)
  - Society for the Study of Labour History (London), undated; 325338 (Box 92)
  - Society of American Archivists: Labor Archives Roundtable, 1977-; 302636 (Box 92)
  - Society of Friends (Quakers), 1928; 380152 (Box 92)
  - Society of People "Shakers", undated; 328339 (Box 92)
  - Society to Eliminate the Economic Causes of War, 1924; 302637 (Box 93)
  - Sociograph Company of America (Chicago, IL), undated; 302638 (Box 93)
  - Soil of Liberty (Minnesota), undated; 302639 (Box 93)
  - Soiuz Voinstvuiushchikh Bezbozhnikov SSSR (Union of Militant Atheists of USSR), 1932; 302640 (Box 93)
  - Sojourner Truth Organization (Chicago, IL): Pamphlets I, 1968-; 302641 (Box 93)
  - Sojourner Truth Organization (Chicago, IL): Pamphlets II, 1968-; 302642 (Box 93)
  - Soledad Brothers Defense Committee, 1970-; 302643 (Box 93)
  - Solidarity (Chicago, IL), 1973; 302644 (Box 93)
  - Solidarity (Detroit, MI) I, 1980-; 302645 (Box 93)
  - Solidarity (Detroit, MI) II, 1980-; 302646 (Box 93)
  - Solidarity (Detroit, MI) III, 1980-; 302647 (Box 93)
  - Solidarity (Detroit, MI) IV, 1980-; 302648 (Box 93)
  - Solidarity: Fourth International, 325374 (Box 93)
  - Solidarity (London/Great Britain) I, 1961-; 302649 (Box 93)
  - Solidarity (London/Great Britain) II, 1961-; 302650 (Box 93)
  - Solidarity (London/Great Britain) III, 1961-; 302651 (Box 93)
  - Solidarity (New York, NY), 2000-; 302652 (Box 93)
  - Solidarity (Philadelphia, PA), 1961-; 302653 (Box 93)
  - Solidarity: A Socialist-Feminist Network, 1981-, 2000, undated; 302654 (Box 93)
  - Solidarity Bookshop (Chicago, IL), 1973, undated; 302655 (Box 93)
  - Solidarity London (labor organization), 1965-; 302656 (Box 94)
  - Solidarity Organizing Committee (New York, NY), 1995; 302657 (Box 94)
  - Solidarity Summer School (Detroit, MI), 1997-; 302658 (Box 94)
  - Solidarity Support Campaign, undated; 302659 (Box 94)
  - Soundoff Tucson Healthcare, 2001; 302660 (Box 94)
  - South Africa Defense Fund (New York, NY), 1958; 302661 (Box 94)
  - South African Freedom Committee, undated; 373084 (Box 94)
  - South African Indian Congress, 1952; 302662 (Box 94)
  - South African Labor Party, 1955; 302663 (Box 94)
  - South East Michigan Coalition of Occupational Health and Safety, undated; 302664 (Box 94)
  - South End Press, 1997-; 302665 (Box 94)
  - South Vietnam Congress of People's Representatives for the Formation of the Provisional Revolutionary Government of the Republic of South Vietnam, undated; 380153 (Box 94)
  - South Vietnam National Front for Liberation, 1965-1973; 302666 (Box 94)
  - South West African People's Organization (SWAPO), 1986; 302667 (Box 94)
  - Southeast Asia Research Center (Berkeley, CA), 1983-; 302668 (Box 94)
  - Southern Africa Liberation Committee, 1977; 302669 (Box 94)
  - Southern Africa Media Center (San Francisco, CA), undated; 302670 (Box 94)
  - Southern California League for Economic Democracy (SCLED), undated; 374752 (Box 94)
  - Southern California Regional Committee to Free Angel Davis, undated; 374761 (Box 94)
  - Southern Center for Labor Education and Organizing (Atlanta, GA), 1998; 302671 (Box 94)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference, 1960-1965, 1971; 302672 (Box 94)
  - Southern Committee for People's Rights (Chapel Hill, NC), 1936; 302673 (Box 94)
  - Southern Conference Educational Fund I, 1945-1976; 302674 (Box 94)
  - Southern Conference Educational Fund II, 1945-1976; 302675 (Box 94)
  - Southern Conference Educational Fund III, 1945-1976; 302676 (Box 94)
  - Southern Conference Educational Fund IV, 1945-1976; 302677 (Box 94)
  - Southern Conference Educational Fund V, 1945-1976; 325383 (Box 94)
  - Southern Conference Educational Fund: Organizer's Library Series, 1967; 302678 (Box 94)
  - Southern Conference for Human Welfare I, 1938-1940; 302679 (Box 94)
  - Southern Conference for Human Welfare II, 1938-1940; 302680 (Box 94)
  - Southern Coop Development Program, 1968; 328343 (Box 94)
  - Southern Elections Fund, the, 1970; 412361 (Box 94)
  - Southern Electoral Reform League, undated; 328347 (Box 94)
  - Southern Exposure, 2002; 302688 (Box 94)
  - Southern Folk School and Libraries (Kenesaw, GA), undated; 302689 (Box 94)
  - Southern Labor Association (Blue Ridge, GA), undated; 302690 (Box 94)
  - Southern Legal Action Movement (Atlanta, GA), undated; 302691 (Box 94)
  - Southern Negro Youth Congress (Birmingham, AL), 1939-1946; 302692 (Box 94)
  - Southern Poverty Law Center (Montgomery, AL), 1972-1985; 302693 (Box 94)
  - Southern Poverty Law Center (Montgomery, AL), 1990-; 302694 (Box 94)
  - Southern Regional Council (Atlanta, GA), 1946-1959; 302695 (Box 94)
  - Southern Regional Council (Atlanta, GA) I, 1960-1969; 302696 (Box 94)
  - Southern Regional Council (Atlanta, GA) II, 1960-1969; 325384 (Box 94)
  - Southern Regional Council (Atlanta, GA), 1974; 302697 (Box 94)
  - Southern Regional Council (Atlanta, GA), undated; 302698 (Box 94)
  - Southern Rural Action, undated; 328372 (Box 94)
  - Southern Student Organizing Committee (Nashville, TN) I, 1966-1968; 302699 (Box 94)
  - Southern Student Organizing Committee (Nashville, TN) II, 1966-1968; 302700 (Box 94)
  - Southern Student Organizing Committee (Nashville, TN) III, 1966-1968; 302701 (Box 95)
  - Southern Student Organizing Committee (Nashville, TN) IV, 1966-1968; 302702 (Box 95)
  - Southern Student Organizing Committee (Nashville, TN) V, 1966-1968; 302829 (Box 95)
  - Southern Student Organizing Committee (Nashville, TN) VI, 1966-1968; 302830 (Box 95)
  - Southern Summer School for Women Workers in Industry, 1932-1937, undated; 302831 (Box 95)
  - Southern Summer School for Workers in Industry, 1937-1942; 302832 (Box 95)
  - Southern Tenant Farmers Union I (sharecroppers), 1936-1940; 302833 (Box 95)
  - Southern Tenant Farmers Union II (sharecroppers), 1936-1940; 302834 (Box 95)
  - Southern Visual Education Service, undated; 325393 (Box 95)
  - Southern Workers Defense Committee (New York, NY), undated; 302835 (Box 95)
  - Southpaw Books: Catalogs I, 302836 (Box 95)
  - Southpaw Books: Catalogs II, 302837 (Box 95)
  - Southpaw Books: Catalogs III, 302838 (Box 95)
  - Southpaw Books: Catalogs IV, 302839 (Box 95)
  - Southpaw Books: Catalogs V, 325394 (Box 95)
  - Southpaw Books: Catalogs VI, 325395 (Box 95)
  - Southpaw Books: Catalogs VII, 325396 (Box 95)
  - Southside Women's Liberation Center, undated; 380158 (Box 95)
  - Soviet Booklets (London), 1958-1963; 380159 (Box 95)
  - Soviet Information Bureau, 1948; 380160 (Box 95)
  - Soviet News, 1945-1955; 380164 (Box 95)
  - Soviet News Booklets (London), 1949-1954, undated; 380167 (Box 95)
  - Soviet Peace Council (Sovetskii Komitet Zaschity Mira), 1963; 302840 (Box 95)
  - Soviet Russia Today: Pamphlets, 1939-1950; 328373 (Box 95)
  - Sozialdemokratischer Eriehungs, U. Schulverein, Freie Schule Kinderfreunde, undated; 302841 (Box 95)
  - Sozialdemokratische Partei der Schweiz (Switzerland), 1959, undated; 302842 (Box 95)
  - Sozialdemokratische Partei Deutschlands I, 1906-1919; 302843 (Box 95)
  - Sozialdemokratische Partei Deutschlands II, 1906-1919; 302844 (Box 95)
  - Sozialdemokratische Partei Deutschlands I, 1921-1925; 302845 (Box 95)
  - Sozialdemokratische Partei Deutschlands II, 1921-1925; 302846 (Box 95)
  - Sozialdemokratische Partei Deutschlands, 1945-1949; 302847 (Box 95)
  - Sozialdemokratische Partei Deutschlands (Social Democratic Party of Germany), 1950; 302850 (Box 96)
  - Sozialdemokratische Partei Deutschlands (Social Democratic Party of Germany), 1951-1956; 302851 (Box 96)
  - Sozialdemokratische Partei Deutschlands (Social Democratic Party of Germany) I, 1957-1959; 302852 (Box 96)
  - Sozialdemokratische Partei Deutschlands (Social Democratic Party of Germany) II, 1957-1959; 325397 (Box 96)
  - Sozialdemokratische Partei Deutschlands (Social Democratic Party of Germany), 1960-1966; 302853 (Box 96)
  - Sozialdemokratische Partei Deutschlands (Social Democratic Party of Germany) I, undated; 302854 (Box 96)
  - Sozialdemokratische Partei Deutschlands (Social Democratic Party of Germany) II, undated; 302855 (Box 96)
  - Sozialdemokratische Partei Deutschlands (Social Democratic Party of Germany) III, undated; 302856 (Box 96)
  - Sozialdemokratische Partei Deutschlands (Social Democratic Party of Germany) IV, undated; 302857 (Box 96)
  - Sozialdemokratische Schulverins Zurich, undated; 302858 (Box 96)
  - Sozialistische Arbeiter Partie (Germany), 1932, undated; 302859 (Box 96)
  - Sozialistische Arbeiter Partie von Nord Amerika (Philadelphia, PA), 1889; 302860 (Box 96)
  - Sozialistische Arbeiterjugend (Germany), 1923; 302861 (Box 96)
  - Sozialistische Arbeiterjugend (Germany), 1932, undated; 302862 (Box 96)
  - Sozialistische Einheitspartie Deutschlands I, 1946-1971; 302863 (Box 96)
  - Sozialistische Einheitspartie Deutschlands II, 1946-1971; 302864 (Box 96)
  - Sozialistische Partie Osterreichs (Austria), 1945-1958; 302865 (Box 96)
  - Sozialistischen Bundes, undated; 380170 (Box 96)
  - Sozialdemokratischenpartei der Stadt Bern, undated; 302866 (Box 96)
  - Spanish Atrocities Committee (Great Britain), 1897; 302867 (Box 96)
  - Spanish Committee of Liberation (New York, NY), 1945; 302868 (Box 96)
  - Spanish Embassy in London, 1936-1937, undated; 302869 (Box 96)
  - Spanish Embassy (Washington, DC), 1945-1949; 302870 (Box 96)
  - Spanish Ex-Servicemen's Association (London), 1960; 302871 (Box 96)
  - Spanish Information Bureau, undated; 380171 (Box 96)
  - Spanish Intellectual Aid (New York, NY), 1939; 325398 (Box 96)
  - Spanish Village Court, undated; 422930 (Box 96)
  - Spark: A New School Student Organization (New York, NY), undated; 302876 (Box 96)
  - Sparks Fly Committee: East Coast, 1998; 325399 (Box 96)
  - Spartacist League of Australia and New Zealand, 1970; 302888 (Box 96)
  - Spartacist League of the U.S., 1964-1968; 302889 (Box 96)
  - Spartacist League of the U.S. I, 1967-1969; 302890 (Box 96)
  - Spartacist League of the U.S. II, 1967-1969; 325400 (Box 96)
  - Spartacist League of the U.S. I, 1970-1971; 302891 (Box 96)
  - Spartacist League of the U.S. II, 1970-1971; 302892 (Box 97)
  - Spartacist League of the U.S., 1972-1980; 302893 (Box 97)
  - Spartacist League of the U.S., 1981-; 302894 (Box 97)
  - Spartacist League of the U.S., undated; 302895 (Box 97)